The Fix. The Gamble. The Betrayal. The Threat.
Even Money is a crime, drama film directed by Mark Rydell.
Gambling addiction bring the stories of three otherwise unconnected
people together as it destroys each of their lives.
Carolyn Carver, played by Kim Basinger.
Detective Brunner, played by Kelsey Grammer.
Clyde Snow, played by Forest Whitaker.
Godfrey Snow, played by Nick Cannon.
Tom Carver, played by Ray Liotta.
Augie, played by Jay Mohr.
Even Money is a 2006 American crime film.
The story concerns three strangers who are addicted to
gambling and how their lives come to be intertwined.
They are a novelist who struggles to write her follow-up book, a former stage
magician and an older brother of a college basketball star.
The film was directed by Mark Rydell, and stars Forest Whitaker, Nick Cannon, Kim Basinger,
Danny DeVito, Kelsey Grammer, Tim Roth, Carla Gugino, Jay Mohr, and Ray Liotta.
It was released on May 18, 2007 in theaters.
The tone is emotional.